[music]
[singing]
[music] Hey guys. Hey guys. Welcome to
the new vloggy vlog. Welcome. [applause]
Welcome. If you're new here, my name is
Damsha and we are vlogging.
We are back to the regular schedule.
Back
this year, let me tell you something.
This year has tried.
It has tried me, but we're still
standing cuz you can't keep a good woman
down. Period. So, we're back. We're
feeling better. Life is good. Life is
rosy.
And we are grateful for everything that
life has to offer.
[laughter]
Um, yeah, we're back to the regular
schedule. Thank you so much for bearing
with me in those I think that's probably
the longest that I've gone without
posting since I started my YouTube
channel. And let me tell you, it was not
intentional at all. It wasn't a break.
It wasn't I was fighting for my life.
Let me tell you something. [laughter]
I am laughing now, but it was not a
laughing matter at a time because Sana,
I was fighting for my life, but you
cannot keep a good woman down. Period. I
haven't posted in like a very long time.
So now I'm doubting everything I know
about vlogging, editing, and everything.
But I feel like the only way we'll get
back to it is by me being consistent
again. So, let's let's do it. Going to
lunch with Hubs and we're also going to
buy some groceries for the week. And I
thought, let me take my camera and start
vlogging so that we can get back.
My husband said I'm going to be fine.
It's like riding a bicycle. I'll be
fine. I'll be fine. Um vlogging again
and editing and basically getting back.
So yeah, let's do that. I don't know
where we having this lunch. There's this
restaurant we went to called Bio. Oh,
Sana. The food was so good. Like it was
so good. I've been fantasizing about it
since. It's like a breakfast brunch
spot. So I think we might go there. I
don't know what hubs have in mind. All
he told me was that.
So
see
you.
Let's go to Woollies.
Let me tell you something. I don't know
how we ended up at Wooies, but we're at
Wind.
And you're doing [music] the same.
No rain, no flowers,
nothing's growing where your heart is
fire. But baby, I bet
[music and singing] you're cold without
me. Even when it's 90°
without [music] me, I bet that you can
get any sleep in the bed lying [singing]
awake. Cuz I'm not there [music] beside
you, keeping you warm. And I know I bet
you're cold.
[music]
You're so damn cold.
It never rains in California.
The sun, [music] it's always shining
bright.
But if the [music] sky would open up,
you're staying [singing] home. You don't
get out. You always [music] used to love
the rain. But LA changed her. No rain,
[music] no flowers,
nothing's growing where your heart is
fire. But baby, [music] I bet you're
cold without me. Even when it's 90°
without [music and singing] me, I bet
that you can get any sleep in that bed
lying awake. [music] Cuz I'm not there
beside you, keeping you warm. And I
know. I [music] bet you're cold.
You're so damn cold.
[music] I bet you're cold.
You're so damn cold. [music]
No [music] rain, no flowers,
nothing's growing where your heart is
fire. But baby, [music]
I bet you're cold without [singing] me.
Even when it's 90°
without [music] me, I bet that you can
get to sleep in the bed lying [music]
awake. Cuz I'm not there beside you,
keeping [music] you warm. I know. I bet
you're cold.
[music] You're so damn cold.
It never [music and singing] rains in
California.
The sun [music] is always shining right.
[music]
I'm back from galavanting with my man
getting some groceries.
We got some milk, some pasta, both
riatoni and penny,
and all gold or nothing. Okay.
And then got some rice cakes just to
snack on. Then we got some meat. Got
fish. This is very nice, especially if
you can put it in the air fryer and have
it with some veggies.
Simple dinner option or even lunch.
And then also for meat, we got some
lamb,
which we'll probably have for dinner.
And then have some chicken
and mint.
This was just some pop up.
And then for Bricky,
I wanted to try this berry musli.
And there's also some old grain
and some smoothies. I've been enjoying
these
mango and granadilla smoothies.
Some yogurt
butter.
And then also for lunch. I'm in my soup
era, guys. I think it's because it's
winter.
Love me a good soup. And this country
vegetable soup one from Woolly's is my
favorite. So I got that
and this just for lunch. It's always
nice to have this in the freezer in case
you want to have lunch quickly and you
don't want to cook. Then got
[clears throat] some potatoes,
carrots,
and some coffee and tea.
some crackers.
>> Yeah,
that is pretty much it. Let me put you
the way.
>> I see it in your eyes.
>> Yeah, I can read the signs.
You need to get away. [music]
It's time to make a change.
Oh, you [music] know you'll always have
me.
>> I'm the goals.
>> Baby, I will always [music] stay with
you.
So, put your trust in me. [music]
We'll work it out. You'll see. If we get
in a car and drive some [music] place
far,
[music]
we don't have to stop. Baby, let's
[music and singing] go for a ride.
You and I. [singing] Let us run away.
We can go where we want.
[music] I'll have your back. If you'll
have mine, you
>> and the daylight. And today is the day
that the Lord has made because I am
finally getting my braids done. I feel
like I've been threatening to do my
braids [music] for some time. I still
haven't done my braids this year. Low
key proud of myself cuz that means I've
been able to just keep it going with the
wigs. And also
my hair needs a relaxer. I haven't
relaxed my hair in such a long time.
I've been doing wig lines back to back
to back and treatments. So I think after
these braids, I'm probably I'm probably
going to relax my hair. And I would love
to do a sew in. Look at me already
thinking ahead. I love it for myself
cuz I'm always like unsure what to do
with my hair. So, I think after these
braids, I'm going to relax my hair and
I'm going to look for bundles so that I
can do a sew in cuz winter is a perfect
time for a sew in. Um, yeah.
[clears throat]
But anyway, today I'm doing braids. I
took down my wig lines.
Um, and I washed my hair this morning.
It was a mission cuz like I said, the
growth
is insane.
But yeah, we're fixing that. Um, one
thing I know for a fact is that a new
hairstyle will always make you feel
good.
All your problems are going to disappear
if you just get your hair done. Okay,
maybe not all of them, but you will
handle them better.
But anyway,
um, o the lady that's gonna do my hair
is almost here. I just want to make
myself some tea. It is a bit cold.
And
I want to be warm and I'm going to sit
and work while I'm getting my hair done.
Period. I'm so excited. I'm going to do
the half up half down [music]
broken
[music]
future.
All the [music] plans you made in your
heart [singing]
grew just to die.
[music and singing]
And now you're damaged goods. Damage
should never [singing]
been. [music]
Thought you were bulletproof. Look at
you. What happened? [music]
Did she hurt you? Are you [music]
okay, [singing]
baby?
[music]
>> Everyone gets [singing] hurt. It's how
we learn to make love [music] work. It's
part [singing]
of
life. [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Baby, don't cry.
No [singing]
[music] more. Just let her walk out.
Baby, don't [singing and music] cry.
Oh, more mama's here.
[music] I wrote a little
to you.
[music]
You're done [music] with
me.
Hey guys. Hey guys. Oh, one thing about
half up, half down.
I feel like
I feel like I'm still enjoying this
hairstyle
and it's already looking a little
cranky. I've only had it for like a
week. I think it's because my hair
needed
to be relaxed so bad. But hey guys. Hey
guys. I did my braids and then I
disappeared.
I did my braids and then I disappeared
on you guys. But we're trying to get
back to being consistent.
I am currently on my way to what's this
place.
I'm on my way to Willies.
I want
I mean granted today it's a bit hot but
we are knee deep in winter and it is
cold and I saw these sweatpants the
other day
that are like yellow
and pinks and blues.
So,
I would be so happy if I were to get
like a cute set today.
Like a
like a winter set.
Oh, Santa, what is happening?
Why is there so many police?
Thank you.
which yeah, that's what we're doing.
Maybe I can even find a knit dress
because
even getting dressed like if you want to
wear a dress is a bit of a mission. So
if I can get a knit dress
and maybe
um
what's this? Maybe a tracksuit or
something.
I would be happy.
But yeah, that's what we're doing. But I
also need matcha.
I need a little bit of a pickme up.
>> I always give away too [music] much.
It's like I've got no sense of touch.
I'm always pouring out my heart.
No, little by little.
Here
[music]
I'm always pushing things too far.
Two, five, six, 10 drinks at the bar.
No boundaries, I get too close.
No. Little by little [singing] here cuz
I give my
little by little [singing]
I pour out my heart.
Little by little here
I always run and hit [music] the wall.
[singing]
I'd rather jump and risk [music] the
[singing] fall.
I see no limits in the sky. [singing]
Little [music] by little
here.
No, no. Got stuck on working on [music]
myself.
thought
that these random summer days
in the middle of winter are actually
quite crazy
because
why is it so hot today?
It's literally 29°.
It's beautiful.
What a car. What a car.
Anyway,
I got the goods. I got the goods. I got
two tracksuits. One blue and the other
one is yellow. I also wanted the brown
one, but they're so expensive. It's like
two 1,000 rand per pop
cuz they sell the set separately. So
yeah, I'll get the brown one later on
and maybe a black one as well
and then I should be fine for winter,
especially for like lounging at home.
And they look like they're good quality.
So
it is what it is. It do what it do.
Okay,
so yeah, let's go home. I want to get
out of this dress and then I'll see what
we'll make for dinner.
I think we'll make pasta or something
quick and simple. Another day, another
salah. Let me tell you something.
[music] I've had these braids for over a
week and they look so raggedy. Let me
tell you why.
It's because I did not
>> relax my hair. Like I haven't relaxed my
hair in like seven months. Kind of like
it like that because [music] I want to
get some growth. I want to get a little
bit of growth and I have to cut my split
ends because [music] my hair looks
crazy.
So I it's probably time for me to relax
my hair, especially if I want to do like
a hairstyle like this.
I am a little bit embarrassed.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm a little bit embarrassed because
Sarah, why does
why does my hair look like this?
I mean, I haven't enjoyed the hairstyle,
but I feel like it's like this is like a
a couple of days, maybe a week if you
can stretch it to if
you have straight hair. um by growth.
But yeah, um I think I'm going to take
these braids down probably. I am
thinking about
um
cuz I have
singles back. I have knotless back. So
maybe I should just remove the front and
make the rest knotless.
Then we can take the braids down. I
don't know.
We'll see. But anyway, I really want to
tidy up the house and bake some banana
bread. The weather allows. It's very
gloomy.
It's very chilly. And then for dinner,
we're going to have
um butter chicken, maybe with naan bread
or with rice. I haven't decided.
Yeah. But for now, I just I really want
to
spruce up that kitchen and make sure
that my house smell like something
baked. I haven't baked in a minute. So,
I think we'll start with
our trusted recipe, [laughter] the
banana loaf recipe, because I have some
ripe bananas there. I hope they're
enough. It's three small bananas. I hope
they're enough. I usually use three
large or four small, but we'll see.
We'll make it work. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Let me know.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat up
>> [music]
[music]
>> here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
[music]
>> [music]
>> It is lunchtime and I'm making
the quickest
I've ever made for lunch. I'm going to
put this crumb chicken snitle in the
snitle. I never know how to say this
name. This thing. I'm going to put this
in the air fryer.
I have this bular wheat and lentil
salad. When I finish that leftover ao
and some
grated beetroot. One thing about me, I'm
a huge fan of beetroot.
So yeah, that's for lunch with my glass
of water.
[music]
I have a visible one.
>> Another ZA. Let me tell you something.
I did not bake that banana bread that I
said I was going to bake yesterday,
but we're going to do it today. My
husband was like, "Don't you forget
today."
Let me show you. I also want to show
you, but
I am also wearing
I'm also wearing those sweatpants that I
got the other day at Woolly's.
Love them.
This is how they look like.
They are long sleeves. They are
widelegged.
They're quite nice.
So, yeah, we're going to make this
banana bread. I have these three ripe
bananas.
Do I still remember how to make this
recipe?
Okay, I think I have everything. I have
eggs. I have my bonantos,
baking powder. I found some flour,
milk,
butter,
chocolate chips,
and vanilla essence,
and some sugar. Sugar. Sugar. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> I watch you as [singing] you drive. Do
you know I'm looking
and I can't help but smile. Do you
[music and singing] know how much I love
you? You put my favorite song on. I
[music] put my feet up
and we just sing along.
[music and singing]
And I can't help but feeling just loving
this moment. Can we stay
[music and singing] here forever?
I'm loving this moment. Can we stay here
together? [music]
If I could stop the time, don't you know
that I would? Cuz I'm just loving
[music] this moment. Can we stay here
forever?
Forever. [music]
Forever.
[music] Forever. [singing]
[music] I watch you as you sleep. You
don't know I'm looking.
With you. [music] Everything's complete.
Do you know how much I love you? I put
your favorite [music] song [singing] on
just to wake you up. When I dance
around, I [music] can't help but feeling
just loving this moment. Can we stay
here forever? [music]
I'm loving [singing] this moment. Can we
stay here together? [music]
If I could stop the time, don't you know
that I would? [singing] Cuz I'm just
loving this moment. Can we stay [music]
here forever?
Forever.
>> I'm loving this moment.
[music] Can we stay here forever?
[singing]
I'm loving this moment.
Can we stay here forever? [music]
We stay here forever.
>> [music]
>> Guess what's for dinner today?
>> If you say butter chicken, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding.
You would be correct. This is how my
banana bread
came out. I was cooling it. I haven't
cut it or anything, but it looks it
looks delish.
>> Oh, Sana, that's beautiful.
>> My banana loaf.
I hope it tastes as good as it looks.
Oh, son.
S guys, my banana bread
came out so nice.
It's so much better than I expected.
Mainly because my batter
was more than my pan.
I mean, less than my pan. So, my bread
is a little bit on the thin side. But
she is nice.
She is fluffy.
She is soft.
And she's delicious.
M.
I want to marinate my chicken.
[music]
My butter
chicken.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I woke up in the [music and singing]
middle of the night.
And I wondered how you're [music] always
right.
It gets me.
[music]
I couldn't see what you saw in me.
[music] Oh [singing] n.
[music] But you showed me how to
believe.
Still gets me.
[music]
When I look back, I can see you're
hiding. [music]
Waiting for a moment [singing] to step
in.
And [music] I'll never understand how
you saw it coming.
[music] Oh,
>> you
will love it.
>> [music]
>> Can I put you on the floor so you can
stay your palms off the floor? [music]
Okay.
[music]
>> It is hard to share my thoughts
now.
[music]
>> It's like cutting in the bleeding.
[music] forgets me.
But I [music] know that you need it all.
Ooh.
Nah nah nah.
Just give me some [music] time cuz I
need to know
that you're staying.
When I look [music and singing] back, I
can see your hiding.
>> Today is my fun Thursday.
Let me tell you something.
>> I do not watch sports.
Well, I do watch only F1. F1 is the only
sport I watch.
Um,
but otherwise, that's it.
That's about it.
>> I only watch
when it's World Cup and I used to watch
cricket growing up
because they were obsessed with cricket.
So now
I don't watch anything. My grandfather
did tell me that are chiefs though. So
that's that's that I know that I know.
But beyond that
when it comes to especially soccer
but today is buff day. My husband really
wants to make us tacos.
But yeah, that is the tea.
I'm about to run a couple of errands
with my man. [clears throat]
[gasps] We have a sick mission that
we're going to
and then
we'll come back and make these tacos.
I'm looking for that small brush so that
I can try and
brush my edges.
Guys, this hair looks so bad. I can't
find this brush. Let me tell you
something.
I'm going to look a bit
crusty.
[music] I see Tuesday
with this.
You need to [music] get away
if we make a change.
Oh, you know [music] you always have me.
Baby, I will always [music] stay with
you.
So, put your trust in me.
We'll work it out. We'll see if we get
in a car and drive some [music] place
far. Yeah, we could go for [singing] a
ride.
The two [music] of us, we don't have to
stop. Baby, let's go for a ride,
[music] you and I. Let us run away.
We can go where we want.
[music] I'll have your back if you'll
have mine. You and I. You [music]
and I.
Want to leave [singing]
everything behind.
If you [music] wanted to.
Promise you we will be all right if it's
you and I. You and I.
[music and singing]
I want you to my
[music]
we can stay in hotels [singing]
just
[music]
only good times ahead.
So let me put a smile upon your face.
Maybe make your [music] worries go away.
[music]
>> Hi guys. Hi guys.
>> We are at Calavaning as per usual.
Just getting our my mini grocery.
>> I'll have [music] your back if you have
mine. You and I. You and I
want to [music and singing] leave
everything behind.
If you wanted [music] to
promise you we will be [singing] all
right if it's you and I. You and I.
>> [music]
>> You [music] and I, let us run away.
We can go where we want. [music]
I'll have your back if you'll have mine.
[music and singing]
You and I. You and I. Back from
gallivanting.
And we topped up. This is the main
reason why we went to the shops. We
needed some
meat.
I still didn't get everything. But we
have beef. I mean, we have chicken. This
is all beef. And then pork.
Um,
I got some chicken snitchel. Guys, this
is such a hack for like a quick lunch or
quick dinner. These chicken snitchell. I
saw someone on TikTok making their own.
Maybe I'll try that. But for now, I just
get these ones and put them in the air
fryer.
And then we got this chicken breast. Got
two of them.
And for mints, we got
three.
This one is mushed together, but it's
it's two. And then this is a third one.
Then we got this beef
for my beef stew. You can never go wrong
with beef stew in winter. Okay. And then
we got these
beef burgers.
These are actually really nice.
And then we'll have a small small bride
tomorrow. Just the two of us with hubs.
So we got chicken breast. Y
we got chicken wings and some wash.
And we'll add whatever else we have to
make that bry.
And then for pork, these pork bangers,
they're so good. So we got 16 of them.
And then we got some
bacon as well.
Love that. This was
buy two and save 20%.
And then got some salad. This is dinner
today.
This creamy spinach and butternut. And
this bular wheat salad has been my
obsession recently.
And then I got some
got some
fruit as well.
And then we got these juice. Cranberry
juice has also been my current
obsession. [gasps] I can't tell you why.
Cranberry juice and guava.
And then
got some double cream yogurt for
smoothies or musli or whatever. And this
one just to snack on.
And then these smoothies always come in
handy for hubs at work or even me
whenever.
So we got these. I got the mango,
mango and pineapple and the strawberry
one.
And then we got some bread, banana and
lemon
topped up on some Italian herbs and
thyme.
tomato paste.
Also, I've been enjoying this beef
bolognese pasta sauce. So, got that as
well, especially for a riatoni. So,
we're going to make a riatoni recipe
with that.
And then also topped up on some coffee
pods,
cheese, butter.
They had a three for two special, so we
had to indulge.
I've been in my cereal era, so we got
some Cocoa Pops. These air fryer
parchment paper
so good if you don't want to constantly
have to wash your air fryer. So, I got
these
and then
um topped up on some cleaning supplies.
We just needed some soap, handy Andy,
and dometos.
That is all we got.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Give me love. [singing]
Give me all your love. Oh, cuz [music] I
want you.
No one else makes me feel this
[music and singing] way. Don't know what
you do.
Hold [music and singing] my hand. Could
you hold my hand? Look me in the eyes.
[music]
Hey guys, another day, another dollar.
Let me tell you what,
I'm taking the front part of my braids
down
because
I'm going to do something [gasps]
something called stop and go. I just
learned where you do half and then
[clears throat]
and then we do half again. But now I'm
going to do [music] um
knotless here in front.
These braids look nice for like two days
only because my hair is severely
severely fat.
[laughter]
It's extremely it needs a relaxer like
yesterday.
So I think that's why this didn't last.
I mean, it lasted like two and a half
weeks. [music]
So, yeah. Let me take it down and then
and also today husband and I well
husband is brying. I'm not. I'm just
being [music] an assistant. I'm just
going to make chalaga and
and potato salad. I'm already done
boiling my potatoes. I'm waiting for
them to cool cool down [music] and then
I'll make a chakalaka.
I'll take down these braids. [music]
And that's pretty much it. I think I'm
going to fold laundry as well and just
chill.
[music] Yeah. Let's take these down so
that I
a person amongst people.
I promise. [music]
who are you
[music]
know
if I'm giving you my love you love
I did a bit of top up from yesterday's
[music] grocery run. Things that we
forgot. I realized that I actually don't
mind the
farmer's choice fresh chicken from
Checkers. So, we topped up on chicken
for a month and then
I accidentally ordered 350 g. I thought
it was 500 g,
but anyway, for smoothie, we got mango
tubes and strawberry.
And then if for bread for my husband
and then
um I'm currently obsessed with Roy Boss.
I don't [music] know if it's because
it's winter or what, but we got that.
And I forgot
fabric softener.
and these baby soft [music]
um thingy toilet paper wet flushable wet
[music] toilet papers
and
basmati rice. This I'm going to use now
a tangy [music]
nola mayonnaise.
What would you do if a guy made asexual?
[music]
>> Life is a winding road.
No telling where it goes.
Driving [music] through days and nights.
Won't stop for traffic lights.
And I
I really want to know really [music]
want to know
if I
ever figure out where the road goes.
[music]
Even if I'm falling down, I will keep on
searching for my [music] highs.
You can say I lost my mind. I will keep
on holding my head high.
>> [music]
>> Even if the sky is falling down,
[music]
Jumping from cliffs so high,
trusting [music] our wings to fly.
Sometimes we're crashing down.
But we get up and start from the ground.
>> My bra for tonight. [music]
I really want to know. Really want to
know
[music]
if I
ever figure out where the road goes.
[music]
Even if I'm falling down, I will keep on
searching for my [music]
highs.
You can say I lost my mind. [music] I
will keep on holding my head high.
>> Sana. Hey guys,
>> it's the next day.
And Santa,
I just finished taking down my braids.
Well, I finished yesterday [music] and I
washed it. I washed them now.
[music]
Hello.
get affordable cream.
>> So, [laughter] I've washed them now and
she is going to come and
do braids here in front. I washed my
hair. [music] Blow dried it
and the works. And now
we're going to do a round two
of the braids. And to be honest, I don't
have the patience. I don't have the
patience to do a full head of
not just braids. So, this works out
perfectly for me.
I hope we can be done in like
three, maybe 4 hours.
Ideally two. Ideally two.
But because my braids are quite long, so
maybe we'll see. I didn't even get a
chance to shower. I literally just wash
my hair. But it's fine. I'll do that
afterwards.
I'll do that afterwards. I'm not going
anywhere today.
[music]
>> You can say I lost my mind. I will keep
on holding my head [music]
high.
Even if the sky is falling down. [music]
Even if the sky is falling down.
Sky is falling [music]
down.
>> [singing]
[music]